Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1975-1990; 1
  - General, 1975-1990; 1
    - 1988-1989, 3
      - Niskala, Thomas, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 37)
      - Oliver, Louise P., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 38)
      - Olsen, Judith L., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 39)
      - Payne, James A., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 40)
      - Perry, Leroy W., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 41)
      - Polson, Lynn, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 42)
      - Prause, Ben E., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 43)
      - Puett, Nelson Jr., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 44)
      - Ramirez, Jesus, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 45)
      - Ramos, Hortencia, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 46)
      - Ratcliff, Jerry, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 47)
      - Robertson, W.L., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 48)
      - Rogers, Thomas G., 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 49)
      - Romo, Ricardo, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 50)
      - Rushing, Doris, 1989 June (Box 103, Folder 51)
      - Schrade, Charles A., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Schwartz, Walter C., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Sellers, Susan R., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Sellers, Wayne C., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Shaw, Judith A., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Shea, B.M. Jr., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Sitka, Henry J., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Skidmore, Sandra, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Smith, Mary Alice, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Spellman, Charles E., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Stage, Dick, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Steen, Lias B. “Bubba”, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Stevens, Marguerite, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Suehs, Thomas M., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Supak, Mary Lee, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Sutton, Ronald L., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Taylor, Elvin J., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Temple, Larry E., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - Townsend, Pat Jr., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - Turner, Loretta, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Vela, Ramon, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 21)
      - Vickers, C. Tom, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 22)
      - Villarreal, Rodolfo, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 23)
      - Viola, Kim T., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Walker, Darlene, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 25)
      - Weiser, Mickey L., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 26)
      - Wells, Odessa, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 27)
      - Westbrook, Pat D., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 28)
      - Whitaker, James V., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 29)
      - Wilcox, Lee D., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 30)
      - Wyatt, Frederica, 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 31)
      - Wynne, Buck J., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 32)
      - Yeager, Wilbur A. Jr., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 33)
      - Young, Bill L., 1989 June (Box 104, Folder 34)
      - Akin, Richard K., 1989 June (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Altiser, Jeanne, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Alwin, Lawrence F., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Anderson, William E., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Appling, Dan, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Arrell, Vernon M. “Max”, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Avery, Donald R., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Babin, Lynda R., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Bean, Richard G., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Benoit, Jo S., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Bingham, Alva, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Bishop, Beth, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Borchardt, Jonita B., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Brainerd, Richard W., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Bridges, Martha R., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Brummett, George G. Jr., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Buie, T. Dan, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 17)
      - Bullock, David R. “Dave”, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Campbell, Al, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 19)
      - Castaneda, Diana, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 20)
      - Cendejas, Robert E., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Chandler, Robert A., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 22)
      - Chenault, Charles V., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 23)
      - Clevenger, Christy, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 24)
      - Close, Jackie, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 25)
      - Coker, Sam, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 26)
      - Connor, Paul, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 27)
      - Cook, Glenn J., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 28)
      - Cook, Suzanne D., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 29)
      - Crawford, Ernie W., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 30)
      - Damelin, Eva J., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 31)
      - David, Irwin T., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 32)
      - Davis, Hugh W., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 33)
      - Denton, B.J. Jr., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 34)
      - Diggles, Walter, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 35)
      - Duggan, Greg, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 36)
      - DuLaney, Bob, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 37)
      - Duncan, Harley T., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 38)
      - Edwards, Betty, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 39)
      - Edwards, Mike, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 40)
      - Emerson, Phillip, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 41)
      - Enochs, George H., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 42)
      - Erskine, John M. Jr., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 43)
      - Evans, Frank, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 44)
      - Evans, Larry Q., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 45)
      - Everitt, Elizabeth, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 46)
      - Field, David D., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 47)
      - Fisher, Wesley S., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 48)
      - Flores, Hector P., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 49)
      - Fritz, Jo Ann, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 50)
      - Fugate, Joyce Wynelle, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 51)
      - Garza, Armando Jr., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 52)
      - Gilter, John Paul, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 53)
      - Gondek, George J., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 54)
      - Gray, Calvin H., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 55)
      - Greanias, George, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 56)
      - Greenfield, Stuart J., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 57)
      - Groneman, Mark, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 58)
      - Gutierrez, Aurora V., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 59)
      - Harrison, John D., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 60)
      - Hedrick, Robert K. Jr., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 61)
      - Helbert, Brad, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 62)
      - Henderson, Glenda, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 63)
      - Henson, Bill J., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 64)
      - Herring, Jane, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 65)
      - Hiller, Carol, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 66)
      - Hittson, Jo Beth, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 67)
      - Hunt, Claudine, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 68)
      - Irvin, John W., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 69)
      - Ius, Julie, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 70)
      - Johnson, A.C., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 71)
      - Johnson, Shirley Ann, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 72)
      - Johnston, Ramon, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 73)
      - Jones, Joy, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 74)
      - Kelly, Don, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 75)
      - Key, Earl A., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 76)
      - Lee, Bob, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 77)
      - Leonard, Robert W. Jr., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 78)
      - Lindsay, Jon, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 79)
      - Lipschutz, Abe, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 80)
      - Luce, Thomas W. III, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 81)
      - Lumbrera, Mary Lou, 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 82)
      - Lundgren, Paul G., 1989 July (Box 105, Folder 83)
      - Mayo, R. Truett, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - McKinney, Michael W., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Mills, Walter R., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Mittendorf, Karen, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Mojica, Joe, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Monroe, Norris, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Morrow, Fred, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Morton, Kenneth C., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Muncy, Analeslie, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Nelson, Roger K., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Notzon, Al J. III, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Oeser, Arthur W., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Onion, James C., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Paradis, Carole, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Paris, David P., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 15)
      - Pelley, Frances, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 16)
      - Perrin, Jack N., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - Pharis, David B., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - Pierce, Jack, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - Pilkington, Jack S., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - Pineda, Carlos R., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 21)
      - Pitner, Gary W., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - Pitstick, William J., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 23)
      - Polson, Lynn B., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 24)
      - Radford, Patricia, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 25)
      - Robbins, W.K. Jr., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - Roberts, John, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 27)
      - Ruland, David, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 28)
      - Rush, Gene, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 29)
      - Samman, Joseph, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 30)
      - Schechter, Harry, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 31)
      - Shown, Janet, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 32)
      - Sides, Eugene H., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Slutz, Carolyn, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 34)
      - Spellman, Charles E., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 35)
      - Steele, Betty, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 36)
      - Steen, Lias B. “Bubba”, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 37)
      - Stevenson, J. Charles, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 38)
      - Tacker, Berry, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 39)
      - Tanner, J.O., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 40)
      - Taylor, Marcus D., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 41)
      - Thompson, Diane, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 42)
      - Thompson, Martha, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 43)
      - Tierney, Cornelius E., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 44)
      - Townsend, Thomas C., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 45)
      - Tucker, Dana T., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 46)
      - Voyles, Linda, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 47)
      - Waddleton, Joe S., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 48)
      - Walker, Carloyn, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 49)
      - Walker, Thomas R., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 50)
      - Weinstein, Bernard L., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 51)
      - Wells, Dorothy, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 52)
      - Wells, Weldon, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 53)
      - Wheeler, Debbie, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 54)
      - Wilchins, Howard M., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 55)
      - Wilde, Dennis, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 56)
      - Williams, John E. Jr., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 57)
      - Williams, Lee E., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 58)
      - Wilson, D. Wayne Jr., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 59)
      - Wood, D.B., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 60)
      - Wyly, Helen, 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 61)
      - Zakarian, Robert B., 1989 July (Box 106, Folder 62)
      - Abington, William, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Ackerman, Linda, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Adams, Paula, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Aikman, John W., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Allaway, William, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Alwin, Lawrence F., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Anderson, Scott, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Andrews, Ken, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Ansley, Angelo N., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Armstrong, Jerry T., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Arvin, Brad, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Basel, Gerald, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 12)
      - Beard, Patricia L., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 13)
      - Beckett, Sheila W., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 14)
      - Berg, Larry L., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 15)
      - Bingham, Bob, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 16)
      - Bingham, Michael R., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 17)
      - Bledsoe, Gary, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 18)
      - Blythe, Mark, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 19)
      - Boswell, Gordon Jr., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 20)
      - Brewer, J.L., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 21)
      - Burke, Cecelia M., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 22)
      - Burton, Henry, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 23)
      - Byrnes, Lorene, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 24)
      - Campbell, Bob, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 25)
      - Campbell, Pat, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 26)
      - Carpenter, Lowry, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 27)
      - Carroll, Edna, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 28)
      - Carter, Wanda E., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 29)
      - Catoe, Paul, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 30)
      - Chapman, Charles W., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 31)
      - Chavers, Dean, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 32)
      - Clark, Brian, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 33)
      - Clary, Johnny Ray, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 34)
      - Cochrane, Jeffrey D., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 35)
      - Collins, Sam F., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 36)
      - Cook, Walter R., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 37)
      - Cooper, Lucille, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 38)
      - Curry, Clarence, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 39)
      - Daniell, Cristy, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 40)
      - Dart, Justin W., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 41)
      - Davis, Winston, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 42)
      - Dedman, Robert H., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 43)
      - De la Garza, Aurora, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 44)
      - Dibrell, Joe B. Jr., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 44)
      - Dunn, Henson, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 45)
      - Emerson, L. Richard, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 47)
      - Escobar, Manuel G. Jr., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 48)
      - Eshbach, Jay M. II, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 49)
      - Freemster, Ronnie F., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 50)
      - Fields, Gloria B., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 51)
      - Fields, Larry M., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 52)
      - Floyd, Robert, 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 53)
      - Franklin, Jack L., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 54)
      - French, Forrest J., 1989 August (Box 107, Folder 55)
      - Gaeta, Patricia, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Gallegos, Leo, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Garza, Antonio “Tony”, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Garza, Ygnacio, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Gaskamp, Jeannine, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Gilmer, Jesse B., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Gooch, William D., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Graff, Stuart L., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Gray, Margie J., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Grossenbacher, William, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Guzman, Virginia, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Hastings, William D., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Hansen, Donald L., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 13)
      - Hart, Ruth Pugliese, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 14)
      - Hassen, Aref, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 15)
      - Hedrick, R. Ken Jr., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 16)
      - Hester, Jean, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 17)
      - Hineman, Bruce, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 18)
      - Hoffman, C.W. Jr., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 19)
      - Hoyt, Thomas G., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 20)
      - Hudson, Michael E., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 21)
      - Hughes, Stephen D., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 22)
      - Hutton, Gary W., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 23)
      - James, John P., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 24)
      - Jenkins, Robert A., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 25)
      - Johnson, N. Warren, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 26)
      - Johnson, Tom, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 27)
      - Kelly, Winston L., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 28)
      - Key, Earl A., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 29)
      - Kimberlin, Sam, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 30)
      - Knight, Barney, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 31)
      - Kozielski, Donald R., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 32)
      - LaFaver, John D., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 33)
      - Lansford, Robert A., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 34)
      - Lawlor, John J., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 35)
      - Leach, Gary J., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 36)
      - Lederer, James C., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 37)
      - Lee, William I., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 38)
      - Leib, Harold, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 39)
      - Lipton, Serena, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 40)
      - Little, Michael R., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 41)
      - Lowden, Maggie, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 42)
      - Lowke, Richard P., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 43)
      - Luce, Thomas W. III, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 44)
      - Luna, Vilma E., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 45)
      - Lyle, Aleatha, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 46)
      - Lynch, Robert A., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 47)
      - Martin, Julian, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 48)
      - Martinez, Leigh A., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 49)
      - McBeath, Sherman, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 50)
      - McMahon, F. Hagen, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 51)
      - McMillon, R.L., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 52)
      - Megason, Marylene, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 53)
      - Merlo, C.E., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 54)
      - Meurer, Ms. A. Cronfel, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 55)
      - Mitchell, John W., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 56)
      - Mobley, William H., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 57)
      - Moore, Michael, 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 58)
      - Morris, Earle E. Jr., 1989 August (Box 108, Folder 59)
      - Odis, Leo, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Owens, Eddy, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Patel, Mohanlal M., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Pierce, Edward D., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Pierson, Joan S., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Pitner, Bonnie, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Polcyn, Valeri, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - Primrose, Wanda, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - Pruitt, Marvin, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Reagan, Harold E., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Regan, Edward V., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 11)
      - Riggins, Ann, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Rivera, Joe, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 13)
      - Roselius, Jay R., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 14)
      - Sarver, James W., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 15)
      - Scanio, Vincent J. Jr., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 16)
      - Schrade, Charles A., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 17)
      - Scopes, Gary, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 18)
      - Sealy, Ray, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 19)
      - Shanklin, Chuck, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 20)
      - Shillingburg, Jim, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 21)
      - Simpson, Riley J., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 22)
      - Sims, Helena G., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 23)
      - Smith, Danny, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 24)
      - Smith, Gary W., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 25)
      - Smith, Geraldine, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 26)
      - Snow, Don, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 27)
      - Stanton, Martha, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 28)
      - Statser, Barbara F., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 29)
      - Steen, Lias B. “Bubba”, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 30)
      - Sterling, C.L. “Lloyd”, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 31)
      - Stewart, Forrest E., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 32)
      - Terchek, Kristin, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 33)
      - Tesmer, Daniel, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 34)
      - Trout, Nancy, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 35)
      - Urbanovsky, Marty, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 36)
      - Van Daniker, Relmond P., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 37)
      - Walker, Dennis J., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 38)
      - Waller, Rhonda R., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 39)
      - Walsh, Allison, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 40)
      - Ward, Betty, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 41)
      - Weigel, John L., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 42)
      - West, Nancy, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 43)
      - White, Barbara, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 44)
      - Wilkins, C.A. “Clay”, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 45)
      - Woodson, Herbert H., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 46)
      - Workman, Harold, 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 47)
      - Yzaguirre, Antonio Jr., 1989 August (Box 109, Folder 48)
      - Advani, Prem S., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Alwin, Lawrence F., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Ashworth, Kenneth H., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Baumer, Michael H., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Bradie, Peter R., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Brasher, Wanda, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Brookmole, Sue M., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - Brown, Richard D., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Carcano, Linda R., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - Casso, Roberto, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - Clary, Johnny Ray, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 11)
      - Coggeshall, Janice R., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 12)
      - Conway, Betty, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - Cook, Alva, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 14)
      - Cook, Walter R., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Costa, Mark A., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 16)
      - Crowley, Brian P., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 17)
      - Curtis, Gary A., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 18)
      - Daines, Darrel, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 19)
      - DeBeauvoir, Dana, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 20)
      - DeJarnett, Kenneth G., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 21)
      - Derus, Margaret M., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 22)
      - Drew, Josephine, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 23)
      - Dunlop, Pamela R., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 24)
      - Dyess, Denise P., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 25)
      - Edwards, James L., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 26)
      - Evans, Larry D., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 27)
      - Gaskins, Junior W., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 28)
      - Ginsburg, Harold H., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 29)
      - Gradick, Jim G., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 30)
      - Graham, Robert L. Jr., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 31)
      - Griffith, Joe E., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 32)
      - Haberer, Ida M., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 33)
      - Hadaway, Karen D., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 34)
      - Hale, William M., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 35)
      - Hanson, Regina S., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 36)
      - Hodges, John E., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 37)
      - Horton, E. Gay, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 38)
      - Hudson, Michael, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 39)
      - Hughes, Janice F., 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 40)
      - Johnson, Sue, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 41)
      - Johnston, Robin, 1989 September (Box 110, Folder 42)
      - Kenney, Thomas J., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Key, Earl A., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Kleinworth, Thomas W., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Kilmartin, William W., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Konvicka, Frank H., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Kretzschmar, G.E., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Lanier, Susan, 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Luce, Thomas W. III, 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Marek, Delfin, 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Mercier, Philip A., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 10)
      - Milanese, Richard P., 1989 September (Box 111, Folder 11)